https://www.wbacorp.com/legal/data-privacy

I am a
DOT Personnel, Government Employee, Owner or Transportation Official
Request Sample or Literature
Current Audience: Specification Writer, Architect or Engineer
Data Privacy
Thank you for visiting the Watson Bowman Acme website! In the interest of transparency, we would like to provide you with the following information related to this specific website as well as general information that applies to your interaction with MBCC Group.
Please be aware that our website and our products and services are directed to individuals in the United States of America and Canada. If you are located outside of the United States of America or Canada and choose to visit our Website or other MBCC Group websites or platforms, or purchase our products or services, or otherwise communicate or interact with us in person or electronically, please be aware that your information may be transferred to, processed, maintained, and used on computers, servers, and systems located outside of your state, province, country, or other governmental jurisdiction where the privacy laws may not be as protective as those in your country of origin, and you do so at your own risk.At Watson Bowman Acme, data protection has the highest priority. This document is designed to provide you with information on how we are following the rules for data protection at Master Builders Solutions, which information we gather while you are browsing our website, and how this information is used. First and foremost: your personal data is only used in the following cases and will not be used in other cases without your explicit approval.
Collecting dataWhen you visit the Watson Bowman Acme website, general information is collected automatically (in other words, not by means of registration) which is not stored as personal related data. The web servers that are used store the following data by default:-The name of your internet service provider -The website from which you visited us-The websites which you visit when you are with us-Your IP addressThis information is analyzed in an anonymous form. It is used solely for the purpose of improving the attractiveness, content, and functionality of our website. Where data is passed on to external service providers, we have taken technical and organizational measures to ensure that the data protection regulations are observed.
Notice Under California Consumer Privacy Act ("CCPA")
Please be aware that by visiting this website or application, Watson Bowman Acme will be collecting certain general information about you and your internet activity for specific business purposes. For a description of the information collected about you and the business purposes for which that information is used, please click here: Table III Data Collection Purpose. For further information about Watson Bowman Acme's overall data privacy practices, please review Watson Bowman Acme's Privacy Policy, which may be accessed here: https://www.basf.com/us/en/legal/data-protection.html
Collecting and processing personal data
Personal data is only collected when you provide us with this in the course of, say, registration, by filling out forms or sending emails, and in the course of ordering products or services, inquiries or requests for material.
Your personal data remains with our company, our affiliates, and our provider and will not be made available to third parties in any form by us or by persons instructed by us. The personal data that we do collect will only be used in order to perform our duties to you and for any other purpose only when you have given specific consent. You can adjust your consent for the use of your personal data at any time with an email to the effect that you revoke your consent in the future to either the email address listed in the imprint or to the data protection representative (contact information listed below).Data retentionWe store personal data for as long as it is necessary to perform a service that you have requested or for which you have granted your permission, providing that no legal requirements exist to the contrary such as in the case of retention periods required by trade or tax regulations.SecurityWatson Bowman Acme deploys technical and organizational security measures to protect the information you have made available from being manipulated unintentionally or intentionally, lost, destroyed or accessed by unauthorized persons. Where personal data is being collected and processed, the information will be transferred in encrypted form in order to prevent misuse of the data by a third party. Our security measures are continuously reviewed and revised in line with the latest technology.
Right to obtain and correct information
You have the right to obtain information on all of your stored personal data, to receive, to review, and if necessary to amend or erase. To do this, just send an email to the email address indicated in the imprint or to the person in charge of data protection (see below for the relevant contact details). The deletion of your personal data will be completed unless we are legally obligated to store the information.
CookiesOn our corporate website, we only use cookies if they are required for an application or service which we provide. If you would like to opt out of the advantages of these cookies, you can read in the ‘help’ function on your browser how to adjust your browser to prevent these cookies, accept new cookies, or delete existing cookies. You can also learn there how to block all cookies or set up notifications for new cookies.
(1) The following cookies are important for the smooth operation and specific services of our website:
Cookie
Purpose
End-of-life
SessionPersistence (CLIENTCONTEXT and PROFILEDATA)
Allows us to save preferences that you set during your visit on our website.
Will be erased as soon as you clear your cache (or one year after your visit)
SessionPersistence (Cookie Layer)
This cookie stores your consent to the use of cookies.
Will be erased as soon as you clear your cache (or one year after your visit)
SessionPersistence (Cookie Disclaimer)
This cookie stores your acknowledgment of and consent to any disclaimers on our website.
Will be erased as soon as you clear your cache (or one year after your visit)
TS < pool_name >
This cookie enables us to distribute the load of requests of our users properly to our servers. It facilitates the stability of our website.
Will be erased as soon as you close your browser
(2) Cookies for web audience measuring:
Cookie
Purpose
End-of-life
ACOOKIE
This cookie allows the web analytics tool Webtrends to collect anonymous information about how our website is used. Such anonymous information shows us inter alia how many people visited our website, the websites that the users were on right before they landed on our website and which pages they visited.
Will be erased two years after your visit
WT_FPC
By default, Webtrends tracks visitors across the primary domain and all sub-domains. This is done by setting a first party cookie on your primary domain with the leading dot, which allows sub-domains to also read this cookie.
Will be erased two years after your visit
Id
We use the DoubleClick cookie to collect data regarding user interactions with ad impressions and other ad service functions as they relate to our website.
Will be erased two years after your visit
utag_main
The Tealium Tag Management library creates and maintains a single cookie called utag_main. Within that cookie are several built-in values that keep track of the anonymous visitor session. Like a unique identifier for the session and a Unix/Epoch time stamp in milliseconds.
Will be erased one year after your visit
D41ID
We use this cookie from Dun and Bradstreet to derive anonymous information concerning businesses visiting our websites.
Will be erased one year after your visit
_ga
Google Analytics registers a unique ID that is used to generate statistical data on how the visitor uses the website.
Will be erased two years after your visit
visitor_id
Pardot tracks visitor activities and cookies are set to remember preferences (like form field values) when a visitor returns to the site. Pardot also sets a cookie for logged-in users to maintain the session and remember table filters.
Will expire after ten years
atidvisitor
This cookie by the analytics tool AT Internet enables the tracking of the list of sites encountered by the visitor and the storage of identified visitor information. If the cookie is deleted, a new visitor is counted for visitors returning to the website as there is a lack of identified visitor information.
Will be erased 6 months after your visit
atreman
Through this AT Internet cookie a prior attribution campaign is being memorized. If the cookie is deleted, the prior attribution of campaigns is not possible anymore.
Will be erased 30 days after your visit
atredir
This cookie allows AT Internet to keep the information which is transmitted during a JavaScript redirect to measure the traffic source. If the cookie is deleted, the information which was transmitted during a redirect is lost.
Will be stored for 30 seconds by default
atsession
This AT Internet cookie collects the list of new campaigns which are encountered during a visit, in order to avoid measuring the same campaign several times. If the cookie is deleted, campaigns which are already encountered during a visit may be sent again.
Will be erased 30 minutes after your visit
atuserid
Through this cookie by AT Internet the Visitor ID for first-party cookie sites is stored. If it is deleted, there is no unique visitor ID for first-party cookie sites available.
Will be erased 13 months after your visit
idrxvr
This third-party cookie by AT Internet allows to collect the main visitor ID through which the cross-domain processing of unique visitors is enabled. The cookie presents the technical value which is linked to the identified visitor management. If it is deleted, there may be changes in the determination of a visit/visitor.
Will be erased 13 months after your visit
tmst
The AT Internet - Timestamp third-party cookie is indicating the date of placement of the main visitor ID cookie. If it is deleted, there may be changes in the determination of a visit/visitor.
Will be erased 6 months after your visit
You may use your browser settings to decide which cookies to accept and to decline. Please be aware that you may not be able to use all features of our website if you decline cookies.
How can I disable AT Internet cookies?
You may adjust your preferences at any time and submit your choice to either enable or disable AT Internet cookies on this page.
Contact
If you have any questions or ideas, please refer to the data protection representative at MBCC Group, who will be pleased to help you. The continuous development of the Internet makes it necessary for us to adjust our data protection rules from time to time. We reserve the right to implement appropriate changes at any time.
The Data Protection Officer at MBCC Group:
Alois MaierMBCC GroupDr. Albert Frank Strasse 3283308 Trostberg, GermanyTel.: +49 (0) 8621 86-2561
alois.maier@mbcc-group.com
10. Who is Controller and Data Protection Officer?You can find the Controller in the meaning of data protection laws here.Please use the address of the Controller above or the following address to contact our Data Protection Officer or Data Protection Coordinator
11. Privacy of ChildrenThis Website is intended to be used by persons aged 18 and older. We do not seek to collect information about persons under the age of 18. No information should be submitted to or posted on the Websites by persons younger than 18 years of age. If such a person submits personal information via the Websites, we shall delete that information as soon as we are made aware of their age and thereafter shall not use it for any purpose whatsoever.
SHARE:
Print
